# Alexandermorris135@gmail.com | Alexander Morris | (727) 455-2422

# Linkedin | GitHub

#### Tampa, FL 33612

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Bachelor's degree with four years plus experience in legal and two years of technical support. Specializing in personal injury litigation, construction litigation, and corporate law Extensive legal knowledge, organization skills, invoicing, accounts receivable, ability to meet timely deadlines, typing speed of 40 - 50 words per minute, preparing case documents, time management, and excellent research skills. Ability to create social media content for the firm and manage podcast(s) for the company. Knowledgeable in multiple coding languages and statistical analysis.

#### SKILLS

- SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL, MSSQL)
- Python (Pandas, matplotlib, NumPy)
- Excel (VLOOKUP, Pivot Tables, Conditional Formatting)
- Tableau
- Google Ads

- Facebook Ads Manager
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Other Skills: Audacity/Audiotronic | SEO optimization | Troubleshooting | State Court Filings (Florida) | Federal Court Filings | Scheduling

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Adams and Reese, LLP Office Services Coordinator

Tampa, FL June 2022 - April 2023

- Assisted over 35 attorneys with case preparation, legal documents, and critical date reminders for cases during tenure.
- Assisted in the management of accounts receivable and accounts payable for the firm.
- Communicated and resolved at least 50 technical and/or operational issues encountered
- Generated billing reports on a monthly basis
- Maintained an organized case filing system.

  Escalated and coordinated unresolved incidents to the appropriate parties
- Managed the purchasing, stocking, and distribution of office supplies.
- Provide on-time status and communication to clients regarding outstanding and resolved incidents.
- Reviewed and proofread legal documents for spelling and formatting errors on a weekly basis for attorneys.
- Undertook a minimum of 10 assigned projects and actively participated in improvement initiatives regarding tools and processes.

Rebein Brothers, PA Tampa, FL Project Assistant Aug 2021 - May 2022

- Collaborated with over 40 clients to gather and track case information during tenure.
- Prepared presentations and summaries of information for attorneys and clients to review case details.
- Identified risks and developed controls to detect and prevent inefficiencies in firm procedures
- Reduced attorney research time by 30% by implementing an archived case system.

  Provided support on case projects by researching and summarizing studies (primarily medical journals) for attorney review.
- Responsible for recording, editing, and uploading 25+ podcast episodes on social media platforms.
- Scanned, converted, and organized records into electronic format with a consistent naming convention.
- Managed resolution of issues efficiently and professionally, manifested by a higher level of customer satisfaction

St. Petersburg, FL Times Publishing Aug 2019 - Aug 2021 Senior Account Specialist

- Utilized account data and service histories to identify trends
- Provided initial assessment, Basic to Intermediate level troubleshooting, and when possible, provided resolutions of inbound issues
- Utilized the company's internal account system in order to track requests, document problems, and record solutions offered to clients.
- Provided consistent performance of the day-to-day tasks and assignments in compliance with established targets and metrics
- Utilized personal expertise and company troubleshooting resolution tree to evaluate technical problems for customers.

#### PROJECTS

#### AdventureWorks Data Analysis

- Utilized a Database in MSSQL to analyze the online transactions of a multinational manufacturing company
- Used Joins, Common Table Expressions, Aggregate functions, and Datatype conversions to drill down and explore data regarding company transactions

#### Food Poisoning Claims Data Analysis

## Certification Project

- Utilized Python and multiple libraries to analyze and alter data related to Food Poisoning claims of a Brazillian fast food chain
- Created multiple views to summarize data

#### EDUCATION

### University of South Florida B.A. Economics

Aug 2018 - May 2022

Tampa, FL

- Member of Judy Genshaft Honors College (2018-2021)
- Member of Black Student Union (2018-2022)
- Emerging Scholars Award recipient (2018-2022)
- Global Tech Experience Digital Marketing Certificate recipient (2021-2022)

#### CERTIFICATIONS

DataCamp Tampa, FL Data Analyst Associate July 2023

- Credential ID: DAA0015911757732
- Relevant Skills:
  - Python (Pandas, matplotlib, NumPy)
  - SQL (PostgreSQL, MySQL, MSSQL)